Finding Aid for Arthur J. Tuttle Papers 1849-1958
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Case Files
  - 1926-June, 1929
    - Nature's Rival v. Jackson Corset Co., 4 folders (Box 7)
      (Patent, Includes transcripts, quite funny, proof involved handling huge numbers of women's corsets and discussing their construction and operation)
    - Parker Rust Proof v. Ford Motor Co., 2 folders (Box 7)
    - Permutit Co. v. Massachusetts Laundry Co. (Box 7)
      (Patent infringement, water softener, photo of Tuttle with the apparatus removed and placed with photo file)
    - Permutit (Box 8)
    - U.S. v. John D. Porter et al., 2 folders (Box 8)
      (Fraud in construction of Camp Custer)
    - Edward Romley, Bankrupt (Box 8)
    - U.S. v. Alexander M. Rovin, 2 folders (Box 8)
      (Citizenship procured by fraud, includes transcript)
    - Aaron Sapiro v. Henry Ford and Dearborn Publishing Co. (Box 8)
      (Famous case, Henry Ford's anti-semitism. Ford accuses Tuttle of discriminating against him as a rich man)
    - Steel Wheel Corp. v. B.F. Goodrich Co. (Box 8)
      (Patent, pneumatic-treaded wheels)
    - Marion Gladys Sutherland v. U.S. (Box 8)
    - Sutherland Paper Co. v. Michigan Carton Co. (Box 8)
      (Patent, machine to make cartons)
    - Transport Truck Co., Receivership (Box 8)
    - George C. Walker v. Lakewood Engineering Co. (Box 8)
      (Patent, concrete road building. This case was reported in Scientific American as demonstrating a wise new way to evaluate the value of patents -- by the innovation in the idea behind the invention rather than the structural similarity to prior art)
    - William L. Walz and Ann Arbor Savings Bank v. Insurance Companies (Box 8)
  - July 1929-July 1933
    - Bendix Brake Co. v. Midland Steel Products Co., 5 folders (Box 8)
      (Patent for vehicle brakes, Includes transcript)
    - Charles C. Blackmore and Jeffrey N. Collins v. General Motors Corp (Box 8)
    - Circuit Court of Appeals
      (Correspondence with Judges Arthur C. Denison of Grand Rapids, Smith Hickenlooper of Cincinnati and Xen Hicks of Cincinnati)
      - Oscar W. Bartee v. U.S. (Box 8)
        (Majority opinion drafted by Tuttle)
      - Bobango v. Erie RR Co. (Box 8)
      - City of Louisville v. Louisville Ry. Co. (Box 8)
      - Commissioner of Internal Revenue v. Alva Bradley (Box 8)
      - H. J. Didinger v. Penn. RR Co. (Box 8)
      - Emch v. Pennsylvania RR Co. (Box 8)
      - Erie RR Co. v. Charles Stewart (Box 8)
      - Fidelity & Deposit Co. of Maryland v. Highland Trust & Savings Bank (Box 8)
      - Charles A. Frueauff v. The Willys Corp. et al. (and Thomas H. Tracy v. The Willys Corp.) (Box 8)
      - Karl H. Hoenig v. Huntington National Bank of Columbus (Box 8)
        (Tuttle dissenting)
      - Harry C. Howard v. Commissioner of Internal Revenue (Box 8)
      - B.F. Kelly v. Aetna Casualty & Surety Co. (Box 8)
      - A.J.W. Manning v. L.M. Ketcham (Box 8)
      - May v. Marbury (Box 8)
      - America Jane McCune v. U.S. (Box 8)
      - Ocean Corp. v. Pearson, Receiver (Box 8)
      - Ohio Galvanizing & Mfg Co. v. Southern Pacific Co. (Box 8)
        (Tuttle drafted the opinion)
      - Camille M. Parker v. C.F. Routzahn, Collector (Box 8)
      - Phillip Carey Mfg. Co. v. Chas. M. Dean, Collector (Box 8)
      - Frank S. Schlicht v. Edward DeGroot & Vacuum Oil Co. (Box 9)
      - Standard Marine Ins. Group v. Scottish Metropolitan Assurance Co., Ltd. (Box 9)
    - Jeffrey N. Collins and Charles C. Blackmore v. Hupp Motor Car Corp. (Box 9)
      (Patent, car curtain rods)
    - Commissioner of Internal Revenue v. Independent Life Insurance Co. (Box 9)
      (Review of Tax Court decision, Tuttle dissents from other two judges, correspondence with Judges Xen Hicks and, Smith Hickenlooper of Cincinnati, Charles H. Moorman of Louisville)
    - Cornell-Coon Construction Co., Bankrupt (Box 9)
    - David Michael and Co. v. Samuel T. Metzger, Mich. Comm'r of Agriculture (Box 9)
      (Constitutionality of rules regulating ice cream, 3 judge panel)
    - Joseph M. Debbins, Bankrupt (Box 9)
    - Frank H. Dehany v. State Highway Commission (Box 9)
      (Condemnation, injunction)
    - Federal Motor Truck Co. v Fred L. Woodworth, Collector IRS (Box 9)
      (Excise tax. Tuttle writes to Dean Henry M. Bates of the U. of M. Law School for advice about construction of statute)
    - James W. Frazier v. City of Bay City (Box 9)
      (Engineering contract for water filtration plant)
    - Fruehauf Trailer Co. Highway Trailer Co. (Box 9)
    - Grand Trunk Western RR Co. v. City of Flint I (Box 9)
    - Grand Trunk II (Box 9)
    - U.S. v. Willis T. Gridley and Gladys Wright (Box 9)
      (Mail fraud, Descendants of Anneke Jans Bogardus convinced to contribute to expense of suit to regain land on which Trinity Church NY, NY stands, letters from the public, newspaper clippings)
    - Edward O. Harris v. Consumers Power Co. (Box 9)
      (Lease for water generated power, Mt. Pleasant, Isabella Co., Michigan, Includes transcript, copy of exhibits)
    - Kellogg Switchboard & Supply Co. v. Michigan Bell Telephone Co. and AT&T, 3 folders (Box 9)
    - James N. Kimball v. Yacht "Denelfred" (Box 9)
      (Maritime liens)
    - Lapeer Trailer Corp. v. Fruehauf Trailer Co. (Box 9)
      (Patent, Includes transcript)
    - M & C Investment Co. v. Wolverine Power Co. (Box 9)
      (Folders 1-4 of 8)
      (Foreclosure and receivership, correspondence. Includes transcript.)
    - M & C Investment Co. (Box 10)
      (Folders 5-8 of 8)
    - Application for reinstatement of Clarence R. Mahrle, Disbarred Attorney (Box 10)
    - U.S. v. William H. McKeighan et al (Box 10)
    - William J. Meagher v. Thunder Bay Quarries Co. (Box 10)
      (Dredging contract)
    - James W. Packard Estate: Marion H. Fisher v. Wilbur M. Bruckner (Box 10)
    - Pearce Stores Co., Bankrupt (Box 10)
    - U.S. v. Olds Motor Works (Box 10)
      (RR freight tariff discrimination)
    - U.S. v. Jack Vassalo and John Mazzalo (Box 10)
      (Liquor, Includes transcript)
    - What Cheer Coal Mining Co., Bankrupt (Box 10)
    - Wyandotte Transportation Co. v. City of Detroit re. Steamer "Conneaut" (Box 10)
  - August 1933-July 1937
    - American Enameled Products, Bankrupt (Box 10)
    - Henry H. Black v. Hugh A. Little, et al. (Dairy regulations) (Box 10)
    - Bay City Brewing Co., Bankrupt (Box 10)
    - Cinderella Theatre Co. v. Sign Writers' Local Union No. 591 (Box 10)
      (Labor injunction)
    - Leon F. Cobb, Bankrupt (Box 10)
    - Flint Hill Brewing Co., Bankrupt (Box 10)
    - Gordon Form Lathe Co. v. Ford Motor Co. (Box 10)
      (Patent for wood lathe, photographs of lathe)
    - Gorney Brewing Co., Bankrupt (Box 10)
    - Great Lakes Steel Corp. v. Frank X. Lafferty, Supervisor of Township of Ecorse (Box 10)
      (Constitutionality of local taxes)
    - Guardian Nat'l Bank of Commerce of Detroit, Bankrupt (Box 10)
    - Hood Rubber Products Co. v. Shoe Market Inc. (Box 11)
    - Huntington College v. Ward Moore et al. (Box 11)
      (Construction of Hattie Cheesbrough's will)
    - Industrial Brownhoist, Debtor, 2 folders (Box 11)
    - John I. Lettich, Farmer-Debtor (Box 11)
    - Midland Brewing Co., Debtor (Box 11)
    - Marvin W. Moestra v. Briggs Mfg. Co. (Box 11)
    - Motor Improvements Corp. v. A.C. Spark Plug, 2 folders (Box 11)
      (Patent for oil filters, discussion of how court transcription is computed and what the prevailing costs were)
    - Rubsam Corp. v. General Motors (Box 11)
      (Patent for demountable wheels with lug-nuts)
    - U.S. v. Certain Lands in the City of Detroit (Box 11)
      (Slum clearance)
    - War Risk Insurance Cases (Box 11)
    - Webster Hall Corp., Debtor, 2 folders (Box 11)
      (Hotel Webster Hall of Pittsburgh. Includes plan of reorganization with exhibits and transcript)
    - William Barie Dry Goods, Debtor (Box 11)
    - Willys-Overland Co., Debtor (Box 11)
  - August 1937-1944
    - Banner Brewing Co., Debtor (Box 11)
    - John Birau, Naturalization Petition (Box 12)
    - Book-Cadillac Properties, Inc., Debtor, 3 folders (Box 12)
      (Correspondence between Tuttle and Arthur H. Cole, librarian of Harvard School of Business Administration, re: collection of plans of reorganization)
    - Cadillac Square Improvement Co., Ltd., Debtor (Box 12)
    - Calvert Fuel & Supply Co., Debtor (Box 12)
    - Condemnation Suits and Resident U.S. Attorney at Bay City (Box 12)
    - Consumers Power Co. v. Saginaw Gas (Box 12)
    - Copeman Labs. Co. v. General Motors Corp. (Box 12)
      (Hard freezing grid patent)
    - Detroit & Cleveland Nav. Co. v. Pere Marquette Carferry (Box 12)
      (Includes "Map of Detroit in Vicinity of Car Ferry Slip")
    - Detroit & Cleveland Nav. Co. v. U.S., 2 folders (Box 12)
      (Includes transcript of 3-judge hearing, suit to set aside ruling of ICC)
    - Jay Eaton, Habeas Corpus (Box 12)
    - Electrical Products Co., Debtor (Box 12)
    - Estey Mfg. Co., Debtor, 2 folders (Box 12)
      (Furniture Co. in Owosso, newspaper clippings)
    - Ford Motor Co. v. CIO (Box 12)
      (Strike at River Rouge Plant 1941 Letters from the public. CIO initiates impeachment campaign against Tuttle after Tuttle granted injunction)
    - General Electric Co. v. Industrial Diamond Co., 3 folders (Box 12)
      (Patent infringement, includes transcript)
    - Greater Detroit Theatres, Inc. v. Co-operative Theaters of Michigan (Box 12)
      (Unfair competition)
    - Greenbaum v. Freud Hotel Co. (Box 13)
    - Luella Hannan Memorial Home v. First National Bank-Detroit and Elizabeth Warren Shelden v. FNB-D (Box 13)
    - Ahmed Hassan, Naturalization Petition (Box 13)
      (Racial designation of Arab immigrant)
    - Carl Houghton, Habeas Corpus (Box 13)
    - James Heddon's Sons v. Millsite Steel & Wireworks, Inc. (Box 13)
      (Fishing lure patent and trademark, Includes transcript)
    - Samuel Enoch Lawrence, Farmer-Debtor (Box 13)
    - Charles C. Legatz, naturalization petition (Box 13)
    - Kurt G. W. Ludecke, Naturalization petition (Box 13)
      (Ludecke published book called I Knew Hitler. Tuttle denied him citizenship. Includes newspaper clippings, letters from public)
    - Maryland Casualty Co. v. Jonathan Cook, et al. (Box 13)
      (Insurance for funds embezzled by Flint city treasurer, Dexter G. Conklin)
    - Masonic Temple Association of Detroit, Debtor, 2 folders (Box 13)
    - Mergraf Oil Products Corp., Debtor (Box 13)
      (Appraisal and Inventory)
    - Metropolitan Life Insurance Co.v Alvinia McDavid et al. (Box 13)
      (Suit of wife who killed her drunken, violent husband for insurance proceeds. Includes transcript)
    - Michigamme Oil Co., Debtor (Box 13)
    - Nelson Bros. Inc. v. U.S., 2 folders (Box 13)
    - Ozark Corp., Debtor, 2 folders (Box 13)
    - Reedley Grape Growers, Inc. v. Central Wholesale Co., Inc. (Box 13)
    - Beatrice Rice v. Nash Kelvinator Corp. (Box 13)
      (Patent, photos of courtroom exhibits of invention)
    - Standard Composition Co., Debtor (Box 13)
    - Superior Drilling & Producing Co., Debtor (Box 13)
      (Gas drilling)
    - Transportation Engineers, Debtor (Box 14)
    - Whiddon v. U.S. (Box 14)
      (War risk insurance case)
    - Lorne John Wright, Naturalization petition (Box 14)
    - Wynn Walters, Inc., Debtor (Box 14)
    - Theodore Zachary v. Arthur J. Tuttle, Arthur F. Lederle, Edward J. Moinet, Ernest A. O'Brien and Frank A. Picard, District Judges of the Eastern District of Michigan (Box 14)
  - A.M. Anderson, Receiver of the Nat'l Bank of Ky of Louisville v. John S. Akers
    (Tuttle designated to take over for Hon. S.J. West February 21, 1933 an enormous case, already in progress)
    - February-December 1933 (Box 14)
    - January-July 1934 (Box 14)
    - August-December 1934 (Box 14)
    - January-June1935 (Box 14)
    - June 1935 (Box 14)
    - July-December 1935 (Box 14)
    - 1936-1938 (Box 14)
    - Pleadings (Box 14)
  - Wm. Barclay Parsons v. Detroit and Canada Tunnel Co., City of Detroit, and County of Wayne
    (Receivership)
    - Case pleadings and correspondence
      - 1932-1934 (Box 14)
      - 1935 (Box 14)
      - 1936-1944 (Box 14)
    - Financials
      - 1932 (Box 14)
      - 1933 (Box 14)
      - 1934 (Box 14)
      - 1935 (Box 14)
      - 1936 (Box 14)
  - Joseph M. Enright v. Michigan Sanitarium and Benevolent Association (Box 15)
    (Dr. John Harvey Kellogg's Battle Creek Sanitarium)
    - Case Pleadings and Correspondence
      - 1933-July 1934 (Box 15)
      - August-December 1934 (Box 15)
      - January-June 1935 (Box 15)
      - July-November 1935 (Box 15)
      - December 1935-April 1936 (Box 15)
      - May-June 1936 (Box 15)
      - July-November 1935 (Box 15)
      - November-December 1936 (Box 15)
      - January-April 1937 (Box 15)
      - May-July 1937 (Box 15)
      - August-September 1937 (Box 15)
      - October-November 1937 (Box 15)
      - December 1937-March 1938 (Box 15)
      - April 1938 (Box 15)
      - May-July 1938 (Box 15)
      - July-September 1938 (Box 15)
      - September 1938 (Box 16)
      - October 1938 (Box 16)
      - November-December 1938 (Box 16)
      - December 1938 (Box 16)
      - 1939-1942 (Box 16)
    - Operating Reports
      - 1933 (Box 16)
      - 1934 (Box 16)
      - 1935 (Box 16)
      - 1936 (Box 16)
      - 1937 (Box 16)
      - 1938 (Box 16)
    - Receiver's Report 1933 (Box 16)
    - Summary of Claims undated (Box 16)
    - Race Betterment Foundation (Box 16)
    - Moratorium Claimants (Box 16)
  - U.S. v. Max Stephan (Box 17)
    - 1942 (Box 17)
    - January-April 1943 (Box 17)
    - May-June 1943 (Box 17)
    - July-December 1943 (Box 17)
    - 6th Circuit Court Appellate Record (Box 17)
    - Application for Executive Privilege (Box 17)
    - Supreme Court Record (Box 17)
    - Letters from Public
      (Numbers in parentheses are counts by Tuttle's office, not BHL inventory)
      - Alabama (2) (Box 17)
      - Arizona (1) (Box 17)
      - Arkansas (2) (Box 17)
      - California (29) (Box 17)
      - Canal Zone (1) (Box 17)
      - Colorado (2) (Box 17)
      - Delaware (1) (Box 17)
      - England (1) (Box 17)
      - Florida (11) (Box 17)
      - Georgia (8) (Box 17)
      - Idaho (2) (Box 17)
      - Illinois (24) (Box 17)
      - Indiana (11) (Box 17)
      - Iowa (10) (Box 17)
      - Kansas (2) (Box 17)
      - Kentucky (1) (Box 17)
      - Louisiana (8) (Box 17)
      - Maine (4) (Box 17)
      - Maryland (5) (Box 17)
      - Massachusetts (15) (Box 17)
      - Michigan (138) (Box 17)
      - Minnesota (4) (Box 17)
      - Mississippi (1) (Box 17)
      - Missouri (7) (Box 17)
      - Montana (6) (Box 17)
      - Nebraska (5) (Box 17)
      - Nevada (2) (Box 17)
      - New Hampshire (1) (Box 17)
      - New Jersey (12) (Box 17)
      - New Mexico (1) (Box 17)
      - New York (63) (Box 17)
      - North Carolina (3) (Box 17)
      - North Dakota (1) (Box 17)
      - Nova Scotia (1) (Box 17)
      - Ohio (23) (Box 17)
      - Oklahoma (3) (Box 17)
      - Ontario (3) (Box 17)
      - Oregon (3) (Box 17)
      - Pennsylvania (28) (Box 17)
      - Rhode Island (1) (Box 17)
      - Saskatchewan (1) (Box 17)
      - South Carolina (2) (Box 17)
      - Tennessee (3) (Box 17)
      - Texas (19) (Box 17)
      - Utah (2) (Box 17)
      - Virginia (11) (Box 17)
      - Washington (4) (Box 17)
      - Washington, D.C. (13) (Box 17)
      - West Virginia (1) (Box 17)
      - Wisconsin (7) (Box 17)
      - Wyoming (1) (Box 17)
    - Bound Briefs (Box 17)
    - U.S. v. Max Stephan: U.S. Supreme Court (Box 17)
    - Max Stephan v. U.S.: 6th Circuit Court of Appeals (Box 17)
- Opinions and Jury Instructions
  The Opinions and Jury Instructions series (2 linear feet) contains Tuttle's opinions and jury instructions for cases which are not represented in the case files series. They are arranged in chronological groupings, then alphabetically.
  - Opinions
    - 1917 (Box 18)
      (check)
    - 1912-1916, 5 folders (Box 18)
    - Writs of Habeas Corpus and Certiorari 1917-1923, 2 folders (Box 18)
      includes case index and newspaper clipping
      (Objections to conscription)
    - 1918-1920 (Box 18)
    - 1921-1923, 3 folders (Box 18)
    - 1924-1925 (Box 18)
    - January 1926-June 1929, 3 folders (Box 18)
    - July 1929-July 1933, 2 folders (Box 18)
    - August 1933-July 1937, 2 folders (Box 19)
    - August 1937-1944, 3 folders (Box 19)
  - Jury Instructions
    - 1912-1917, 4 folders (Box 19)
    - 1918-1920, 2 folders (Box 19)
    - 1921-1933 (Box 19)
- Topical Office Files
  The Topical office files series (21.3 linear feet) includes files kept in Tuttle's chambers arranged by subject. They largely contain correspondence among court officials concerning the administration of the court. Tuttle's tenure saw an explosion in the extent of the Federal bureaucracy and this series documents the development of the bankruptcy court, the Prohibition Department of the Internal Revenue Service, Federal prison, probation and parole systems, immigration and naturalization procedures, the District Court Clerk's office, and the Justice Department and the Administrative Office of the U.S. Courts. The number of judges of the federal bench in Detroit was increased several times during his tenure and his "Additional Judge" files reflect his advocacy for new appointments. Tuttle's secretary usually pinned together incoming queries and copies of Tuttle's replies, allowing a clear record of intellectual interchange. The files relating to "New Federal Office Building" include floor plans and inventories of his chambers.
  - 1912-1920
    - A-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 20)
    - Admiralty Rule (Box 20)
    - Attorney General (Box 20)
    - B-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 20)
    - Baldwin, Julia M.-Expenses of (Box 20)
    - Bankruptcy, Miscellaneous (Box 20)
    - C-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 20)
    - Clerk of the Circuit Court -- Detroit (Box 20)
    - Clerk of the Circuit Court -- Bay City (Box 20)
    - Cole, J. Herbert -- Special Agent, Dept. of Justice (Box 20)
      (Successor Arthur L. Barkey)
    - Cudlipp, Mrs. Louise (Box 20)
    - Custodians (Box 20)
    - D-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 20)
    - Denison, Hon. Arthur C. (Box 20)
    - Department of Justice (Box 20)
    - Department of Justice Circulars (Box 20)
    - Detroit Bar Association Grievance Committee (Box 20)
    - E-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 20)
    - F-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 20)
    - Federal Parole Officer (Box 20)
    - Flint U.S. Commissioner (Box 20)
    - Ford English School (Box 20)
    - Ford Motor Co., Miscellaneous (Box 20)
    - G-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 20)
    - H-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 20)
    - Hurd, J. Stanley, U.S. Commissioner for Detroit (Box 20)
    - I-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 20)
    - Internal Revenue Dept. (Box 20)
    - J-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 20)
    - Jackson U.S. Commissioner (Box 20)
    - Joslyn, Lee E., Referee in Bankruptcy, 3 folders (Box 20)
    - Judge, Additional, 2 folders (Box 20)
      (Correspondence with Judges DuVal West of San Antonio, J.W. Warrington of Cincinnati, Arthur C. Denison of Grand Rapids, Clarence W. Sessions of Grand Rapids, John M. Killits of Toledo, John E. Sater of Columbus, Loyal E. Knappen of Grand Rapids, statistics regarding heavy case burden of Eastern District of Michigan, pleas for assistance)
    - K-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 20)
    - Killits, Hon. John M. (Box 20)
    - L-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 20)
      (Congressman E.C. Little, Judge K.M. Landis)
    - M-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 20)
      (Congressmen J.W. Fordney, Carl E. Mapes, and Earl C. Michener; Detroit Mayor James Couzens; and Judges J.W. Warrington, J.M. Morton, Jr., Alfred J. Murphy)
    - Messenger (Box 20)
      (Judge James C. Wilson)
    - Military Cases and Gen. Correspondence with War Dept. (Box 20)
    - Miscellaneous Subjects (Box 20)
    - N-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 21)
    - New Egyptian Portland Cement Co., Bankrupt (Box 21)
    - Naturalization Matters (Box 21)
      (Senator Charles E. Townsend; Congressmen Isaac Siegel, J.W. Fordney; Chief Naturalization Examiners for Chicago, Fred J. Schlotfeldt, and W.H. Wagner. Tuttle's speech for the Sons of the American Revolution February 28, 1916)
    - O-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 21)
    - P-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 21)
    - Paroles (Box 21)
      (Congressman Augustine Lonergan)
    - Passports (Box 21)
    - Pere Marquette, Receivership (Box 21)
    - Port Huron U.S. Commissioner (Box 21)
    - Post Office General Delivery Nuisance (Box 21)
    - Probation System (Box 21)
    - R-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 21)
    - Regal Motor Car Co., Bankrupt (Box 21)
    - Receivers, Trustees in Bankruptcy (Box 21)
    - Referee in Bankruptcy
      (Lee Joslyn, George Marston and Paul King)
      - 1915 (Box 21)
      - January-October 1916 (Box 21)
      - October-December 1916 (Box 21)
      - January-April 1917 (Box 21)
      - May-December 1917 (Box 21)
      - 1918 (Box 21)
      - 1919-1920 (Box 21)
    - Referee in Bankruptcy: Appointment of New (Box 21)
    - S-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 21)
      (Senator Frank B. Kellogg, Gov. Albert E. Sleeper, Congressman Frank D. Scott)
    - Saginaw U.S. Commissioner (Box 21)
    - Samuel Merchant Co., Bankrupt (Box 21)
    - Sandford, Hon. Edward T.: Gift to Judge Warrington (Box 21)
    - Sayres, William S., Jr.--Standing Master in Chancery (Box 21)
    - Second National Bank of Saginaw (Box 21)
    - Selling, Bernard B.--Resolutions (Box 21)
    - Senatorial Contest Matter (Box 21)
      (Ford vs. Newberry)
    - Sessions, Hon. Clarence W. (Box 21)
    - T-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 21)
    - Telegrams (Box 21)
    - U.S. Attorney (Box 21)
    - U.S. Commissioners (Box 21)
    - U.S. Marshal (Box 21)
    - W-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 21)
    - Warrington, Hon. John W. (Box 21)
    - West Publishing Co. (Box 21)
  - 1921-1925
    - A-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 21)
    - American Bar Association (Box 21)
    - American Civil Institute (Box 21)
    - American Law Institute (Box 21)
      (Tuttle comments on the First Restatement of Contracts as well as an article that he had written about the Institute. Invitation to a reception at the White House during a meeting of the Institute, 1925)
    - American Prison Association (Box 21)
    - Americanization Committee (Box 21)
    - Anonymous Letters, 2 folders (Box 22)
    - Attorney General (Box 22)
    - B-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 22)
      (Judges Joseph Buffington, Francis E. Baker)
    - Baldwin, Julia -- Expenses (Box 22)
    - Bankruptcy
      - Anonymous letters (Box 22)
      - Appraisal of Furniture (Box 22)
      - Auctioneer -- Official (Box 22)
      - Bonds (Box 22)
      - Depositary (Box 22)
      - Examination of Office (Box 22)
      - Financial Reports (Box 22)
      - General, 2 folders (Box 22)
      - Referees in Bankruptcy
        - 1921 (Box 22)
        - 1922 (Box 22)
        - January-June 1923 (Box 22)
        - July-December 1923 (Box 22)
        - 1924 (Box 22)
        - January-February 1925 (Box 22)
        - March-December 1925 (Box 22)
      - Rules (Box 22)
    - C-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 22)
      (Judges Alexis C. Angell, A.M.J. Cohran, W.H.S. Thomson, Frank Cooper; Congressman Louis C. Cramton)
    - Circuit Court of Appeals Dockets (Box 23)
    - Clerk of Circuit Court-Bay City (Box 23)
      (Clarence J. Petit)
    - Clerk of Circuit Court-Detroit (Box 23)
      (Elmer Voorheis)
    - Commissioner, U.S. (Box 23)
      (Frank Quinn, J. Stanley Hurd)
    - Custodian (Box 23)
    - Customs Office (Box 23)
    - D-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 23)
      (Acting Mayor of Detroit, Joseph A. Martin)
    - Denison, Hon. Arthur C. (Box 23)